export const quizeQuestions = [
    {
        question: "When is Diwali usually celebrated?",
        options: ["October", "November", "December", "January"],
        correctAnswer: "November",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the other name for Diwali?",
        options: ["Holi", "Eid", "Deepavali", "Christmas"],
        correctAnswer: "Deepavali",
    },
    {
        question: "Which Hindu god is associated with Diwali?",
        options: ["Vishnu", "Shiva", "Ganesha", "Lakshmi"],
        correctAnswer: "Lakshmi",
    },
    {
        question: "What does the word 'Diwali' mean?",
        options: ["Festival of Lights", "Festival of Colors", "Festival of Fireworks", "Festival of Sweets"],
        correctAnswer: "Festival of Lights",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the traditional Diwali sweet made of lentils and jaggery?",
        options: ["Gulab Jamun", "Jalebi", "Laddu", "Chakli"],
        correctAnswer: "Laddu",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the significance of lighting lamps on Diwali?",
        options: ["To keep away mosquitoes", "To celebrate a cricket match", "To welcome Lord Rama", "To confuse evil spirits"],
        correctAnswer: "To welcome Lord Rama",
    },
    {
        question: "Which animal is associated with Diwali celebrations in Nepal?",
        options: ["Elephant", "Cow", "Dog", "Ox"],
        correctAnswer: "Cow",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the special Diwali prayer or worship ceremony?",
        options: ["Aarti", "Namaste", "Puja", "Mantra"],
        correctAnswer: "Aarti",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the traditional Diwali decoration that signifies good luck and prosperity?",
        options: ["Candles", "Rangoli", "Balloon", "Confetti"],
        correctAnswer: "Rangoli",
    },
    {
        question: "In which Indian epic is the return of Lord Rama celebrated during Diwali?",
        options: ["Mahabharata", "Ramayana", "Bhagavad Gita", "Arthashastra"],
        correctAnswer: "Ramayana",
    },
]